hey everyone caffeine made here and
today I got a good one for you guys
a long one what a good one and with 300
milligrams of caffeine sounds like a
great competitor in the pre-workout
world but not only that there are
actually a decent amount of nootropic
ingredients in here so this actually
could be good for the gaming community
too I mean there was a lot of stuff for
focused energy a lot of cognitive
functions too so could this be for
pre-workout and for gamers
maybe we'll find out hello again
everyone thank you so much for joining
me today and if you want to stay
informed on all things caffeine related
feel free to hit the subscribe button
down below I post new videos every
Tuesday night so what can you expect
from today's video we're going over
bucked up energy and there is so much
information to go over I'm actually
gonna skip the company information I
hope you guys don't get mad at me for
that but there are a lot of ingredients
to go over so I'm gonna be going over
the ingredients and there's six drinks
to review so I gotta get through this
stuff fast I'm gonna be talking pretty
faster in some of the video so hope you
guys can keep up and like I said these
things have a lot of ingredients and
they're good for pre-workout and they're
good for gamers I'm not sure we're gonna
have to look at the ingredients in depth
to find out and if I miss anything
listen these ingredients have pages and
pages of information on the internet
about what they do so I'm gonna try and
condense all those pages into just a
couple of sentences or a couple of
paragraphs for you to give you a good
feel of what they do so if I miss
anything
just know I'm trying to give you a good
sense of what the ingredients do not
everything that they do timestamps down
below so you can go where you want to go
alpha sized alpha GPC it's registered
trademark so you know what's gonna be
good I'm gonna call it a GPC just for
short and a GPC is very special nutrient
that's been shown to significantly
increase acetylcholine levels in the
brain IC o---- : can help improve ki
brain functions such as memory
concentration learning recall and focus
a GPC has this interesting thing called
mind to muscle or a boost Mushka output
sharpens agility it also delays mental
fatigue it also helps reduce HGH human
growth hormone beta alanine the beta
alanine increases carnosine an amino
acid with antioxidant
immune system boosting properties
currency helps reduce acidity in the
muscles during intensity exercises
battalion also improves physical
performance in delese muscle fatigue
however scientists are still trying to
determine why beta alanine may work for
soma exercises as opposed to others
specifically in regards to shorter
duration exercises and longer duration
exercises caffeine isn't it a little
early to go over caffeine
o alphabetical order caffeine 300
milligrams of caffeine enough said
deer antler velvet alright guys let's
talk about this one I know you wanna
know about this one deer antler velvet
has been used in Chinese medicine for
thousands of years it's said to have
beneficial healing properties because it
contains igf-1 which stands for innocent
like growth factor basically a growth
hormone is traditionally used to boost
the immune system as well as reduce
stress which has definitely had proven
results with its also been known to help
impotency and infertility in women now
around 2012 2013 Ray Lewis an NFL player
if you didn't know mentioned it in an
article that he used it in the whole
world went crazy the stock and deer
antler went up because more people
started using it professional sports
started banning the stuff because they
didn't have enough research on it
but now in 2020 many years later and
lots of research being done on it
there's still no conclusive evidence
that deer antler velvet helps with
athletic performance now there have been
lots of studies done of course some
saying this some saying that but like I
said there's been no conclusive
improvement by the proper medical
facilities that do the testing that says
that it works because it's still simply
no concrete evidence I mean that being
said nobody even knows the proper dosage
of it I looked at dozens of different
websites trying to find out what the
proper dosage is and it goes anywhere
from two doses of 250 to 350 milligrams
a day should help maintain your health
and alleviate minor fatigue so around
500 to 700 a day but they say higher
doses are needed for healing and/or
performance enhancement and that typical
dosage is 1 to 3 grams a day so it's
really going to be a matter of how much
is in this drink
Ian does it actually really work dinah
mean dinah mean is another patented
product and it's the patented form of
Aria let's try this out okay methyl uber
in its beginning a lot of hype lately
because of all the stuff that it can
actually do I mean overall is actually a
nootropic ingredient because it does a
lot for the brain but it also does a lot
for the body which is why it's in
workout supplements so this one can be
an ingredient for the gamers as well as
the pre-workout people in a quick
overview the benefits of this ingredient
is improved performance increased energy
increased cognition elevated mood no
crasher jitters and it's basically
similar to TIA cream except it's
supposed to be faster acting than Tia
cream and harder hitting than Tia green
as well as a shorter duration it's also
similar to caffeine based on the energy
that it does provide but that caffeine
comes from the Kuchar tea leaf which is
different than the camellia sinensis
plant that plant is black tea green tea
and white tea you would have known that
if you watch my tea talk series but
noneya did and it also kicks in faster
than caffeine in about 15 to 30 minutes
now unlike caffeine diet Amin is
strictly neuro activating so it doesn't
affect heart rate blood pressure or
vasoconstriction now in stimulating the
central nervous system but not the
cardiovascular system it doesn't
negatively impact your adrenals
adrenaline Dalls yeah sure look it up a
50-50 chance if there's too much of a
toll put on your Adrenaline's to
adrenaline or fatigue it might be
adrenal when you experience adrenal
fatigue stimulants don't work as well
you'll feel sluggish all the time and a
whole lot of other negative stuff that
you probably don't want taurine taurine
is used in a decent amount of energy
drinks because it's been shown to remove
waste products that lead to fatigue and
cause muscle burn although it doesn't
specifically give you energy it reduces
fatigue so some people consider that
gaining energy but it also helps support
brain function therefore good for gamers
and working out l-theanine you guys know
I love it and if you didn't know now you
do l-theanine is an amino acid is most
commonly found
in green tea black tea a couple of
different fun guys
I mean mushrooms and what's so good
about it it is one of the top
ingredients for mental focus and
concentration research has found that
taking just 100 milligrams of l-theanine
in combination with 50 milligrams of
caffeine can improve people's focus
number skills and alertness you know who
else likes l-theanine right in an
interview in early 2019 in Elle magazine
Taylor Swift admitted that she takes
l-theanine for stress and anxiety so or
Taylor Swift likes it shouldn't you two
l-theanine and caffeine 100% for gamers
pre-workout likes it to take rain Hey
I just talked about this this is
Dynamite's little sidekick so to speak
tea cream offers similar stimulating
effects as caffeine and Dyna mean it
does many of the same things that
diamine does but it comes on slower than
Dyna mean and caffeine does therefore
its stimulating effects last for about
six to ten hours long lasting energy and
it enhances concentration and focus
sounds like a fortnight marathon the May
huperzine a huperzine a is another
nootropic ingredient that helps with
acetylcholine signalling which helps
support memory and cognitive performance
Korean red ginseng now bucked up will
tell you that Korean red ginseng is an
ancient homeopathic remedy and
considered to be the most effective
ginseng on the market grown 100%
organically over the course of six years
Korean red ginseng contains a high
amount of active powerful elements
although it's more expensive than
ginseng grown elsewhere we refuse to put
anything subpar in our drinks let the
other guys do that listen guys Korean
red ginseng is panax ginseng yeah
the panax ginseng is then heated with
steam and then dried which helps
heighten anti-inflammatory properties
but really it does all the same stuff
that panax ginseng does and it is in
monster rock star and plenty of other
energy drinks as for the price they
mentioned well they go look how much
more expensive it is glad they're using
good
alright the ingredients list now I know
I just went over a bunch of the
ingredients but I'm actually gonna go
over the list now I don't normally do
this but I do have a reason why I'm
doing it so let's go the ingredients
list have to show the ingredients in
order of what's in there the most all
the way down to what's in the least
obviously your first ingredient is
carbonated water natural and artificial
flavors and citric acid has the first
three next though on the list of fourth
one is beta alanine you need between 2
to 5 grams of beta-alanine to be
effective when working out so is there 2
grams in here I'm not sure but there's
got to be a bunch of is the fourth
ingredient on the list got a good chance
next is taurine now in general companies
don't mind putting a decent amount of
taurine in there because it's not really
all that expensive if you need about one
to two grams of taurine which is what
the energy drinks put in there therefore
I expect there to be one to two grams of
taurine in here because why not put it
in and since it's right after beta
alanine and we're hoping that they're
putting enough beta alanine in there it
is safe to say that it does have the
proper dosage of taurine in it next on
the list it's going to be caffeine now
we know that there's 300 milligrams of
caffeine
thus anything above the caffeine has
more than 300 milligrams and it's been
below caffeine obviously has less than
300 milligrams right after caffeine is
sucralose I heard that these are fairly
sweet than this sodium benzoate okay
and then there's tea racine an effective
dose of tyrosine is between 150 and 300
milligrams so this could definitely be
within that dose because it's right
below caffeine so far so good for
looking like most of these ingredients
not Pixy dusted next is the ace K which
is always gonna be lower than the suger
Louis anyway theanine now we already did
talked a little bit about theanine in
the proper dosage and the truth is you
really only need between 50 and 100
milligrams a theanine to be an effective
dose in when combined with caffeine
it actually works even better and we
know it's gonna Cathy in here therefore
there is probably the exact amount of
theanine in there that you need probably
around 100 milligrams of theanine
because why would you put more than the
effective dose in there
if you don't have to so we're safe to
say we're at 100 milligrams or lower for
any of the rest of the ingredients
now the next six ingredients of all
last six ingredients and we're already
at a baseline that we think is around
100 milligrams and unfortunately the
last six ingredients are all those
premium high quality brand name
registered trademarked ingredients so
after telling you all those awesome
things that they do
are they pixie Dustin or they giving you
our proper dosage the last six so well
let's try and figure it out as mentioned
you know that deer antlers should
probably have about 500 milligrams or
higher and this is nowhere near 500
milligrams because because caffeine is
300 you see how high that is and even if
it did have a lot more it still it still
hasn't still hasn't really been proven
to improve athletic performance X on
that one
the emphasize is a premium acetylcholine
and a minimum dosage of città choline to
be effective is between 250 and 500
milligrams of silicon so not enough in
here
dinah mean recommended dosage is between
100 and 200 milligrams twice a day and
many of the pre-workout supplements
usually have 300 milligrams of it so
once again not really enough in this
drink at probably under a hundred
milligrams Tia cream dosage is between
50 milligrams and 200 milligrams and
it's okay to be on the lower side of
that if you're gonna be combining it
with caffeine because it helps the
effects so perhaps there is a decent
dosage of tea occurring in here to be
effective and huperzine is last on the
list so I'm not gonna worry about that
so all those premium brand name ones
that they actually promote doesn't seem
like there's gonna be enough in there to
be beneficial but that being said don't
forget this has a lot of ingredients and
a lot of them aren't at the proper
dosage so even though some of them don't
have the effective dosages like I said
it's still good to get them in there is
still a lot of beneficial ingredients in
here for pre-workout people and for
gamers I don't know why this hasn't been
I don't know why this hasn't been
promoted by more gamers in general let's
taste them out just need to go grab them
out of the campus protein fridge and if
you actually like these drinks and you
wanna and you're trying to find them you
can actually get them at campus protein
last time I checked campus protein is
selling them cheaper than the bucked up
website and
you can save 10% off your purchase using
coupon code caffeine man 10 first up is
gonna be the great gains right that is
really good I'm getting a little bit of
a grape juice in there but uh maybe the
carbonation and the sweetness is given
it almost like grape soda feel but it's
not like a powerful grape soda like some
of the other grapes that tastes like
grape soda they punch you in the face
with a grape soda flavor and on this
really pulls back on that grape soda
flavor to give you a little bit of juice
and it's actually it's really good it's
got a medium to high carbonation as for
that sweetness it is a medium to high
sweetness and it's really close to that
high category but still at the highest
point of the medium category but yeah
it's really good and then the flavor
profile it's a high flavor profile and
they're doing some good things in here
like I said they're not making it like a
sickly sweet
grape soda and they're not really going
the route of making it like a full-on
grape juice flavor it's kind of a 50/50
of both and it ends up being like really
refreshing I'm definitely a fan of it
and I definitely like it I mean I've
been talking I there's been several
grapes you'll see them on the caffeine
Ranger people you'll see they've been
several grapes and they pack a punch of
grape so if you like grape those other
guys they pack a punch of grape flavor
in there but sometimes it's too strong I
actually really like the fact that this
is a solid grape flavor and it's giving
you a mix of different grapes so Wiz is
going to be going on the caffeine man
rating chart I really like it I'm know
I'm normally not into grapes but if
someone offered me this I would say you
know what yeah yeah I'll take a great
bucked up and that means it's gonna be
going on the caffeine rating chart at I
can't believe I'm saying this for a
grape I've said it for a couple of
grapes so I'm gonna give it a 9.1 great
job with the grape moving on next up
we're gonna be going for the killer Oh J
and typical caffeine fashion once I do
the grape I do the orange next because
for some reason those two always seem to
be paired together I don't know if it's
cuz I Fanta or what it is but it's
always those orange and grape flavors
all right I say it now again I can smell
the orange from here so it's gonna be
strong yeah yeah it that's that's a
strong punch of orange flavor right
there and I'm noticing it's a it's
actually a little bit uh see that that
should a little bit cloudier than the
other one
still relatively clear for pre-workout
drink and yeah back to the flavor and
everything else medium to high
carbonation I will not talk about
carbonation anymore because they're all
gonna be the same for the sweetness
we're going medium to high sweetness as
well but because of that citrus is
actually pulling it back from that high
so it's much more of a medium sweetness
because it's replacing some of that
sweetness with some orange citrus flavor
ice with that flavor profile I'm
actually gonna go with high fever
profile on this now once again similar
to the grape they did not go the route
of making it like an orange soda you're
actually getting an actual orange flavor
in here and it is much more of a solid
almost like an orange juice kind of
flavor without that strongest acidic
juice flavor even though there is a
little bit of acidity in here but it's
not even that acidic it's giving you a
light bit of acidic citrus and overall
yeah I'm very impressed with this one as
well so let's go ahead put this on the
caffeine man rating chart so we're going
with a 9.0 still a the grape a little
bit better but 9.0 still good for that
killer OJ next up we're going for the
blue razz a staple and most energy drink
lines I used to be a big blue razz fan
but I've tried so many of them now and a
lot of fun tastes so similar to each
other that I'm starting to realize there
are other flavors out there that are a
bit better than blue razz and it's good
to uh expand outside of your comfort
zone and try new things I still think
this is going to be good and based on
but with I just got going this way I was
even going towards me
all right this has given you a solid
blue radish flavor so think of some of
your favorite blue Reds is that you've
had and this is gonna be competitive
with it it's given you a solid blueberry
is giving you a solid raspberry it's
giving you a definitely a solid berry
flavor and similar to the grape it's a
it's actually it's kind of light and
refreshing so it's a medium to high
sweetness but it's hovering around that
medium to high area and it's saying I
don't want to be too high just yet which
i think is just the right amount of
sweetness anything that ends up being in
that hi sweetness category can be just
too much by the time you're at the end
of the drink and I think that in these
drinks you're getting just enough
sweetness so that it's gonna balance out
by the end of the drink flavor profile
I'm gonna give it a high flavor profile
it's not super strong and blue razz
flavor to knock you out with flavors
hand OS blue rats it's like oh wow
that's blue razz it's really good so
where's it going on the caffeine man
rate and try given this 19.3 I don't
know guys looks like these are all gonna
be in the nine if they keep it up like
this
who cares if just a couple of the
ingredients aren't as effective as they
should be I'd buy this alone just on
taste next up will be going for the
rocket pop
[Music]
it is definitely rocket pop if you were
to drink this in a blind taste test
you'd be like hey that's a rocket
popsicle all the rocket pops tend to try
and go stronger in some flavor than
others I don't know if they do market
research to see which flavors they like
better I think each rocket pop if you
were to do a taste test of all the
different rocket pops next to each other
each one of them is gonna be a little
stronger and one thing than the other
some of the rocket pops focus on that
red cherry strawberry flavor other ones
focus on that blue blueberry flavor some
of them focus on that white flavor and
that white flavor is similar to a like
the ISIS and stuff similar to like say a
white monster and the Arctic ice flavors
that a lot of the companies go with and
I would say if I had a percentage this
one out I would say this is probably 50%
white probably 30% of that blue flavor
and then maybe 20% of that red flavor
and I'm gonna finish that up to see if
I'm right on that red flavor me maybe 35
on the blue and 15 on the red so you
definitely get a white and blue with a
little bit of red because you know the
Reds usually at the top it's the tip so
there's got to be just a little bit less
of it so you yourself a medium to high
sweetness I'm not gonna talk about the
medium to high sweetness anymore either
for the last couple because they all
really seem to be going for that medium
to high sweetness on the customer height
the only one that was a little bit less
was the orange because of the citrus so
that's two things we don't have to worry
about now we can just worry about the
flavor profile which is me telling you
about the flavor and this one's got a
medium to high flavor profile some of
the other ones had a high flavor profile
this is medium to high so where's our
gonna be going on the caffeine man
rating chart I'm gonna give this one an
eight point eight I hate to take it out
of the nine category but um I'm not a
huge fan of the arctic's and the whites
and since this is like fifty percent of
that and it has that citrus flavor it's
not for me if you're someone who likes
the white monster and those Arctic's and
stuff you're probably gonna read this
higher you're probably gonna put it in
the nines and it's definitely worth the
shot if you guys like those flavors and
you like rocket pop it's still a great
liner drink so far moving on
next up we're going for the blood
as I'm really not sure what to expect
from this one it's got red on there
blood is red Raz so I'm thinking it's
some kind of red raspberry flavor but
it'll be interesting to see what it is
all right I really like that right from
the first sip it's got it's got a
powerful flavor profile to it you
already know the other things so yeah
it's a strong flavor profile I'm
definitely getting some raspberry out of
it but definitely getting some other
stuff too I'm not sure if it's cherry
strawberry I'm thinking about all the
red since it's red on there and I should
probably think of some other stuff too
like grapes and stuff nope not grape not
tropical not you know it's red it has
definitely got the red flavors in there
they haven't been that many strawberry
drinks that have come out there's been a
couple and I think maybe it's because
strawberry mixes with other things and
no one's just done like a straight-on
strawberry flavor raised it or
strawberry Coolatta which was a little
bit tropical and in strawberry but
anyway this I get a little bit of
strawberry in here a little bit of
cherry a little bit of raspberry and I
think I think because I was looking for
one forever to WoW me see if the wow
he's in here you get like a hint to
watermelon but whatever it is maybe
because it's blood razz they just want
to go for all of the reds because they
can't have cherry red raspberry water
and strawberry all in one drink but yeah
I mean if you guys if you guys are
looking for a red drink there you're
getting some you definitely gettin some
reds out of here I wish I could be more
descriptive in it reminds me of when you
buy this starburst just the red ones
because you know starburst she always
has some of the colors that you didn't
like and eventually they realize that
and they just started selling oh here
the purple ones oh here are the red ones
and you get like three different red or
pinks and stuff like that it's kind of
what you gettin out of here you're
getting a couple of different reds and
Pink's so where's it going on the
caffeine man rate and try I would
definitely buy I'm the guy that buys
that red and pink starburst I don't buy
anything else besides those for the
starbursts and that's what I'm drinking
right now so I'm giving this one nine
point four favorite of them so far let's
move on to that last one last up guys we
got the wild orchid orchard orchard
orchid orchard wild orchard orchid has
less letters in it from Rhode Island
originally Massachusetts we like to add
our
and take ours out we parked the car and
I'm not getting into all of them
Wow okay I have to talk about the
sweetness because that is a high
sweetness and I don't mean high
sweetness like horrible but uh in that
medium to high category it's definitely
not me in the medium it's probably like
a medium - if you if you rate Highness
by a low medium and high
you're getting kind of like a medium
high but it's not sickly sweet flavor
profile also a high flavor profile I
would say out of all of these this one
probably has the highest sweetness to it
and close to the highest flavor profile
all of these are really solid in flavor
and I'm gonna go back in to try and pick
out some of those flavors because I
thought it was gonna be a sour apple
that's why I was saving it till last I
was a big fan of the rain sour apple and
and the apples have really been
surprising me lately uh America had a
really good Apple as well I wasn't
expecting to be surprised by how good
some of the apples are but this is not
just an apple there may be some pear in
there too last time I went apple picking
I grabbed two pears while I was there
and go back in yeah you would definitely
you're getting pear in there they
haven't been many pear drinks are the
only one that I actually can remember
off the top of my head is the red belt
hair and the red belt hair is absolutely
awesome it's sugar-free it's actually
like my second favorite one with all the
red balls
so yeah it's got some pear in there and
it's got the Apple in there too so if I
had to say it I mean I'd have to guess
the percentages are kind of like a 50 50
maybe even 60 40 because I mean I didn't
want to have to go in the third time
I'll jump cut the third one out there
there's a third flavor in there and I
can't really pick it out because the the
pear is probably like a 60% pear the
Apple is like a 30% Apple maybe a little
bit of that grape but not like a purple
grape like you know look at the green
grapes maybe it is definitely really
good racking my brain for you guys
trying to get some more flavors out of
here but let's just go pear apple with a
surprise flavor in there as well
definitely has three flavors to it let's
go ahead and put this on the caffeine
man rating chart this one is definitely
the most interesting one out of them
it's definitely flavorful and I am
actually gonna rate this one I
9.5 yeah I do like it the best out of
all these I've been sitting here trying
to think of which one I like the best
but I actually am surprised that grape
is right up there if I had to say the
top three I'm going with the wild
orchard the blood grass and that great
games I never thought I'd say that I
actually like a grape
but that grape it's very unique and
there you have it guys those are the six
drinks from bucked up this drink is an
awesome drink this is ranking right up
there I mean I'm actually gonna say that
for the pre-workout drinks this would
probably be in my top three if I worked
out but for flavor purposes it's in my
top three and if I had to rank those my
top company is rain my second one is
banging and then this bucked up is
really it's really competing with bang
with their flavors a bang is gonna have
a much more punch to their flavors these
are gonna be a lot more solid flavors
you really getting some really solid
refreshing flavors out of here
and truth be told I did actually say
that these drinks were for gamers too
they have a lot of actual they have a
lot of great ingredients for gamers so
you gamer guys out there tell all your
friends that they should be trying this
drink out if they're not already talking
about it on Twitch and such if I was
looking at these and I was looking at G
fuel oh my goodness I've only had four
the G fuel cans I do plan on reviewing
the next four when they come out I'm
trying to get them but I actually do
like these better than the G fuels don't
don't don't write your hate comments
down below because I know I haven't
actually tasted the powders which people
say the powders are even better than the
cans but I don't do powder
I think bucked up makes a powder I don't
do it this is a great drink if you guys
think you know somebody that's gonna
like this drink some gamers and stuff
and they're scared of how long the video
is tell them to use my timestamps that's
what they're there for share this
because you got to get the word out
about bucked up if people don't know
about it yet I'm serious great drink and
if you're looking to purchase it you can
use my link down below to go to campus
protein save 10% off so I can't say
enough good things about it I would love
to say more good things about it I'd
love to recommend more stuff but I got
all those I got all those I got all
those all those milligrams going through
me right now I drank more than I should
have I was only supposed to sip each one
but they were so good I had a second sip
and then some of them I had a third set
so I I got more than 300 milligrams
going through
now trust me but yeah all in the nines
guys except for that one and the the
average of them all are in the nine so I
gotta go I'm talking way too fast
this video is way too long I'm positive
of it so deep breath thank you guys for
joining me I appreciate each and every
one of you until next time you guys have
yourselves a great day or night
and it also and it also helps reduce hd8
and it also helps produce HGH g' HGH HGH
and also helps produce that HGH
which is different than the Camila
census plant which is different than the
Camellia sinensis plant which is
different than the Camila senescence
plant sinensis sinensis sinensis which
is different than the Camellia which is
different than the Camellia sinensis
plant
it is much more and it's much more like
a solid spit on me talk about my hands
you